worldofmods.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy policy

This privacy policy outlines how information collected through our site is both used and protected. Information which we request from users, or information that is made available to us will be used with accordance to this policy.

## Information Collected

While registering on our site, users will be required to submit an e-mail address.  
When signing in through oAuth provider, users will be authenticated using their unique ID of the provider.

## How We Use Your Information

The information we collect may be used to personalize your experience with our site, while providing additional user functionality. E-mail addresses are used as a method of notification.

## Do We Disclose Any Information to Outside Parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or providing information to you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

## Third Party Links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include third party links or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## Third Party Advertising

We use third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our site. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

## Cookies

Our site uses cookies for collecting data, and to enhance our service.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

_Last modified 19.01.2016_

* * *
